https://clearpointhealth.ca/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Welcome to www.clearpointhealth.ca, the official website of Clearpoint Health Corporation and all affiliate websites (the “Website”).THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY DESCRIBES THE ClearpointHealth.ca PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THE WEBSITE AND ALL AFFILIATE WEBSITES.ClearpointHealth.ca reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. ClearpointHealth.ca will notify visitors of changes to this Privacy Policy by providing notice of the change for at least two weeks on the website at www.clearpointhealth.ca.Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy will mean you agree to be bound by such changes. We will also update the Privacy Policy and our privacy practices to comply with federal and provincial privacy legislation as they each may apply. This Privacy Policy was last modified on January 2, 2008.Your privacy is important to us and our commitment to safeguarding your privacy is reflected in this Privacy Policy. Although our ability to provide certain service may requires that we collect personal information about our customers, we take measures to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of that information. At ClearpointHealth.ca we are committed to undertaking reasonable measures to protect the privacy, accuracy, reliability and security of all of the personal information that is provided to us and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Please read the following description of our policies and practices regarding your personal information.A. IntroductionClearpointHealth.ca will only use personally identifiable information about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Personally identifiable information is information about you that can be attributed to you. In this Privacy Policy, personally identifiable information about you will be referred to as “Personal Information”. We do not collect sensitive Personal Information, such as racial or ethnic origin or Health or medical data. The Websites have various features and services. Many of these features and services are available to all visitors to the Website. Some features and services may only available to those that have registered with the Website.B. Collecting, Use and Disclosure PracticesWherever possible, ClearpointHealth.ca will identify the purposes for which Personal Information is collected at or before the time the Personal Information is collected. For some of our Personal Information collection, use and disclosure practices you may be given an opportunity to indicate your wish to limit our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information.We may use Personal Information for the purpose for which it was provided and certain other activities which are reasonably ancillary to such purpose. For example, if you send us an e-mail with a question or comment, ClearpointHealth.ca will use your e-mail address to respond to you. Further, ClearpointHealth.ca may store your e-mail and e-mail address and a copy of our response for future reference.We may request Personal Information from you such as name, home address, telephone number e-mail address, age, income, interests and gender for purposes such as newsletter, chat room, contest and auction registration, and for participation in other interactive online activities as well as to enable us to market various goods and services to you. Despite the fact that the Personal Information may have been provided or collected for other purposes, we may use Personal Information provided to ClearpointHealth.ca to better understand your needs and preferences and provide to you information about future ClearpointHealth.ca events and other items that ClearpointHealth.ca believes that you may be interested in, including the events of similar organizations, or to recommend particular products and services. All of this may be tailored based on your Personal Information.Unless you have opted out, from time to time we may share your Personal Information with other businesses, including our affiliates, marketing partners and advertisers. We will only share such information with these third parties whose policies regarding Personal Information are consistent with our privacy policies and where we have your express or implied consent to do so.ClearpointHealth.ca has engaged agents and certain service providers to assist with its activities (such as fulfillment companies). Further, ClearpointHealth.ca may work with other organizations similar to itself towards some common purpose consistent with its objectives. For these purposes, ClearpointHealth.ca may disclose your Personal Information to these agents, service providers and other organizations. However, ClearpointHealth.ca will require that these agents, service providers and other organizations agree that they will only use and disclose your Personal Information solely for those purposes, that they will not be permitted to use it for any other purpose and that they will adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.Unless you have opted out, we may also use your Personal Information to send you offers from our corporate marketing partners and other business partners. In addition, from time to time we may share your data with certain of these partners so that they may send you offers directly.We may analyze Personal Information and other data in order to enhance ClearpointHealth.ca’s events, services and the Website.From time to time, we may place a “cookie” on your computer. Our third party service providers and ad servers may use cookies as well. A cookie is a file written to your computer’s hard drive that can be used to track your Internet activity. Also, if you submit Personal Information to the Website (such as your name, interests or preferences), we may use cookies to keep track of such information so that you will not need to reenter this information during subsequent visits. We may use cookies to customize delivery of our Website content and advertisements and for other internal site administration purposes. In addition, our ad servers, or those of our third party service providers, may use information about your visits to the Websites and other websites to customize delivery of advertisements to the Websites and other websites.You may elect not to have such information used by our ad servers for such purposes by making an e-mail request to that effect directed to by calling 1.833.666.7874
or email us at info@clearpointhealth.ca. You may also set your Internet browser preferences to notify you when you receive a cookie or decline acceptance of cookies. However, if you decline acceptance of cookies you may experience less than optimal performance of the Websites.ClearpointHealth.ca may also use and disclose Personal Information that is relevant to a legal proceeding or as permitted or required by law.In the event ClearpointHealth.ca transfers control of any or all of its operations or services, ClearpointHealth.ca reserves the right to transfer and disclose your Personal Information to that party. However, ClearpointHealth.ca will require that party to agree that it will be similarly bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy and that it will only use and disclose your Personal Information as ClearpointHealth.ca is similarly entitled under this Privacy Policy.In the event ClearpointHealth.ca amalgamates with another organization, ClearpointHealth.ca reserves the right to permit that amalgamated organization to continue to use and disclose your Personal Information. However, ClearpointHealth.ca will require that the amalgamated organization agree that it will be similarly bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy and that it will only use and disclose your Personal Information as ClearpointHealth.ca is similarly entitled under this Privacy Policy.C. Consent for Collection, Use or DisclosureWhen you voluntarily provide us with your Personal Information, we assume you consent to its collection, use and disclosure in accordance with this Privacy Policy, subject to any collection, uses and disclosures from which you have opted out. In some circumstances, we may expressly request your consent to certain collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information or provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such practices. In some limited circumstances where authorized or required by law, we may collect, use or disclose your Personal Information without your consent.We respect the right of each fan to control how his or her Personal Information is used. If, for example you do not want us to collect your Personal Information, provide it to our affiliates, or if you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you may, in some circumstances be able to opt out at the time the Personal Information is collected. Understand that you can withdraw your consent at a later date, unless legal requirements prevent this or give us particular directions regarding your Personal Information. To do so, contact us at by calling 1.833.666.7874
or email us at info@clearpointhealth.ca. However, not allowing us to collect or use this information about you may mean that we may not be able to provide you with certain products and services.D. Limiting CollectionClearpointHealth.ca will limit the collection of Personal Information to that which is necessary for the purposes identified by ClearpointHealth.ca and pursuant to this Privacy Policy.E. Limiting Use, Disclosure and RetentionClearpointHealth.ca will not use or disclose Personal Information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual to whom the Personal Information relates in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as required or permitted by law.ClearpointHealth.ca will retain Personal Information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected or as required by law. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, ClearpointHealth.ca will not sell, rent, loan, trade, lease or otherwise transfer any personal information, including e-mail addresses, to any third party and ClearpointHealth.ca will treat any Personal Information you provide as confidential information.F. Security SafeguardsOnly authorized employees and agents of ClearpointHealth.ca who need access to your Personal Information in the course of their duties will have access to the information. We have security measures in place against unauthorized access, use, disclosure, alteration, loss or destruction of Personal Information under ClearpointHealth.ca’s control. These measures may include technological, physical and organizational methods of security. However, due to the nature of the Internet and the limits of technology ClearpointHealth.ca cannot guarantee that these security measures will not be breached in all circumstances.G. Access to your Personal InformationUpon request, you have the right to confirm whether or not ClearpointHealth.ca maintains or controls any Personal Information relating to you and whether such Personal Information has been used or disclosed by ClearpointHealth.ca.Further, if ClearpointHealth.ca does maintain or control any Personal Information relating to you, you have the right, upon request, to access such Personal Information and to request correction of any erroneous or out-of-date Personal Information about you. In some limited circumstances as prescribed by law, we may not be able to grant you access to your information.ClearpointHealth.ca pledges to investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of Personal Information and to comply fully with the legal or regulatory supervisory authorities responsible for enforcing our adherence to the privacy principles stated above.H. Third Party LinksPlease note that the Websites and affiliated websites contain links to websites that are not operated by ClearpointHealth.ca. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, and we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site and that you confirm that the site’s policies are acceptable to you.I. GeneralThe Website is operated by and for the benefit of Clearpoint Health Corporation, our affiliates and corporate sponsors. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “ClearpointHealth.ca” shall mean ClearpointHealth.ca.For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the “Website” shall mean http://www.clearpointhealth.ca.Nothing contained in this Privacy Policy is intended to create a contract or agreement between ClearpointHealth.ca and any user visiting its website or providing Personal Information in any form.This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of Ontario and those of Canada applicable therein, without reference to their conflicts of laws. If any provision of this Privacy Policy is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed from this Privacy Policy and the remaining provisions shall remain in full force and effect. Headings are for reference purposes only and shall not be used in the interpretation of this Privacy Policy.J. Contact UsIf you have any comments or questions about our privacy or security practices or about your Personal Information in our control, including its accuracy or integrity, or if you wish to change your preferences as to how we use and disclose your Personal Information, contact us by calling 1.833.666.7874
or email us at info@clearpointhealth.ca.
Sign up for our newsletter today to stay up-to-date on
the latest news from Clearpoint Health's experts
SIGN UP TODAY
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Menu
About Us
Careers
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Copyright © 2020 Clearpoint Health Network. All Rights Reserved.
Clearpoint Health offers a nationwide network of surgical centres to provide easy access and follow-up care to patients. Our vision is to meet growing healthcare needs by delivering exceptional patient care and health outcomes.
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Youtube
Linkedin
